Guide to the Miscellaneous human sexuality periodicals,circa 1950-2003
Miscellaneous human sexuality periodicals,circa 1950-2003
- Triangle, The (The Monthly Newspaper from Gay & Lesbian Community Services of Central Florida, Inc. Serving Orlando's Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Community) (Box 8)
  Publication City: Orlando, FL
- TRICCAD (Tri-County Citizens Against Discrimination) (Box 8)
  Subject: 1990s, Gay liberation movement, Legal, Politics
  Publisher: Tri-County Citizens Against Discrimination Inc. (TRICCAD)
  Publication City: Brooksville, FL
- True Colors: A Newsletter Recommending Gay & Lesbian Resources (Box 8)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Community
- True Police Cases (Box 8)
  Subject: Erotica, 1950s, Heterosexual
  Publisher: Fawcett Publications, Inc.
- True Police Yearbook (Box 8)
  Subject: 1950s, Erotica, Heterosexual
  Publisher: Fewcett Publications, Inc.
- TSA Nesletter (Tri-State Alliance) (Box 8)
  Subject: 1990s, Gay, Lesbian, Alternative local newspaper, News
  Publisher: Tri-State Alliance, Inc. for Gays and Lesbians
  Publication City: Evansville, IN
- Tucson Gay Newsletter (Box 8)
  Subject: 1970s, Alternative local newspaper, Gay, Lesbian
  Publication City: Tuscon, AZ
- Turf (The Zine of Techno Urban Radical Fairies of Washington DC) (Box 8)
  Subject: Entertainment, Gay, Lesbian, 1990s, Zine
- Twin Cities Gay and Lesbian Resource Guide (Box 8)
  Subject: Directory, Community, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual
  Publisher: University Lesbian/Gay Community Minneapolis, Minnesota
- Twin Cities Gaze (The News Bi-Weekly for the Gay/ Lesbian Community) (Box 8)
  Publisher: GAZE Media
  Publication City: Menneapolis/St. Paul, MN
- TWISL Magazine (This Week in Greater St Louis) (Box 8)
  Subject: 1990s, Gay, Lesbian, News, Entertainment, Bisexual
  Publisher: Kacmer Publishing
  Publication City: St. Louis, Missouri
- Twist (Box 8)
  Subject: Entertainment, Gay, Lesbian, 1990s
  Publisher: Twist Magazine, Inc. (Two Twisted Guys)
  Publication City: Rego Park, NY
- UMass GALA News (A Publication of U. of Massachusetts Gay, Lesbian Bisexual Alumni/ae) (Box 8)
  Subject: College/University, 1980s, 1990s
  Publisher: University of Massachusetts Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual Alumni/ae
- UMTFA (Upper Manhattan Task Force on AIDS / English Language / Spanish Language) (Box 8)
  Publisher: Upper Manhattan Task Force on AIDS, Inc.
- Understanding Homosexuality (Box 8)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Gay liberation movement
- Unidad (Gay and Lesbian Latinos Unidos) (Box 8)
  Subject: Latina/Latino, Gay, Lesbian, 1980s, Alternative local newspaper, Community
  Publisher: Gay and Lesbian Latinos Unidos
- Unisun Magazine (Box 8)
  Subject: 1980s, Gay, Lesbian, Community, Directory
  Publisher: UNISUN
- United for the Nineties (Box 8)
  Subject: Pride Parade and Events, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Community, 1990s
  Publisher: Stonewall Union
- United Newsletter, The (Box 8)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, 1980s, Community
  Publisher: The United
- Unity (The quarterly newsletter of The United) (Box 8)
  Subject: Lesbian, Gay, Community
- University of Illinois GALA News (Box 8)
  Publisher: University of Illinois GALA
- Update (Box 8)
  Publication City: (Toronto, Ontario)
- UPDATE (Published by The Body Politic Free the Press Fund) (Box 8)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Gay liberation movement
  Publisher: The Body Politic Free the Press Fund
- UpFront (Box 8)
  Subject: Gay, Entertainment, 1970s
  Publisher: UPFRONT Publishing Co.
  Publication City: Pensacola, FL
- Upfront America (Box 8)
  Subject: 1980s, Alternative local newspaper, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, News, Entertainment
  Publisher: UpFront America, Inc.
- US Department of Justice Pride Update (Box 8)
  Subject: Pride Parade and Events, Government Publication(s), Occupation Based Organizations, 1990s
  Publisher: US Department of Justice Pride
- US Regulatory Reporter (Regulatory Information for the pharmaceutical, medical, chemical & allied industries) (Box 8)
  Subject: Medicine, Health, HIV/AIDS, 1980s, Occupation Based Organizations
  Publisher: PAREXEL International Corportaion
- US Women (Making the most of our lives.) (Box 8)
  Subject: Women, 1990s, Politics, News, Gender Issues, Hetersexual
- UWSLGA Newsletter (Upper West Side Lesbian and Gay Association) (Box 8)
  Subject: Community, Politics, Gay, Lesbian, Legal, Politics, Gay liberation movement, 1980s
  Publisher: Upper West Side Lesbian and Gay Association (UWSLGA)
- V: The Magazine of the Tenderloin (Box 8)
  Subject: 1960s, Gay, Lesbian, Gay liberation movement, Politics, Legal, News
  Publisher: Vanguard, Inc.
- Venereal Disease Information (Box 8)
  Subject: Health, 1940s, Government Publication(s), Safer sex
  Publisher: United States Public Health Service (USPHS)
- VID News (Village Indepedent Democrats) (Box 8)
  Subject: Gay liberation movement, Gay, Lesbian, 1980s, Politics, Legal
  Publisher: Village Independent Democrats (VID)
- View Magazine: A Chronicle of Gay and Lesbian Life (Box 8)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, 1990s, News, Entertainment
  Publisher: The View from Here
- Virginia Advocate, The (Box 8)
  Subject: Religious, Gay, Lesbian, Religious: Catholic, Religious: Baptist, News, Alternative local newspaper, 1980s
  Publisher: The Virginia Advocate, Inc.
  Publication City: Charlottesville, VA
- Virginia Gayzette, The (The Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgender newsmagazine for the rest of us.) (Box 8)
  Subject: Community, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender, News, Alternative local newspaper, Entertainment, 2000s
  Publisher: The Virginia Gayzette, Inc.
  Publication City: Richmond, VA
- Voice (Kansas Information Services & Lesbian/Gay Alliance) (Box 8)
  Subject: Community, Gay, Lesbian, 1980s, News, Drag
  Publisher: Kansas Information Service & Lesbian/Gay Alliance
  Publication City: Wichita, KS
- Voice of ASH, The (Alcoholism Services for Homosexuals, Inc.) (Box 8)
  Subject: Chemical Dependency, Health, 1980s, Gay, Lesbian
  Publisher: Alcoholism Services for Homosexuals, Inc.
  Publication City: Garden Grove, CA
- Voice of the Eagle (Box 8)
  Subject: s/m, Entertainment
- Voices of Women (Box 8)
  Subject: Feminist, Literary
  Publication City: (Kenosha, WI)
- W/E Newsletter (Women's Effort) (Box 8)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Health, 1990s, Women
  Publisher: Women's Effort
  Publication City: Mattydale, NY
- WACHIVIY News (Washington Area Consortium on HIV Infection in Youth) (Box 8)
  Subject: HIV/AIDS, Education, Youth
- Warehouse Newsletter (Box 8)
- WBAI 99.5 Folio (Box 8)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, 1990s
- Weekly Guide, The (Entertainment and Resources for Gay and Lesbian New Orleans) (Box 8)
  Subject: Gay, Lesbian, Directory, 1990s
  Publisher: Life in New Orleans
- Wega Video (Catalogue) (Box 8)
  Subject: Erotic films, Mass media
- Western Express, The (Box 8)
  Subject: 1980s, Alternative local newspaper, Gay, Lesbian
- Western States Center Views (Box 8)
  Subject: News, 2000s, Gay liberation movement, Politics, Legal
  Publisher: Western States Center
- Whazzup! Magazine (Box 8)
  Subject: Gay male, Entertainment, Black, African-American
  Publisher: Whazzup! Magazine
- Where It's At: Fire Island (Box 8)
  Subject: Directory, 1970s, Gay, Gay male
  Publisher: Downing's Where It's At, Inc.
- White Lightning (Box 8)
- William M. Mercer Meidinger Hansen, Inc.: The Bulletin (Box 8)
- Wingspan (Tuscon's Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual and Transgendered Community Center) (Box 8)
  Subject: Community, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender, News, 1990s
  Publisher: Tuscons' Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual and Transgender Community Center
- Wisdoms Child New York Guide (Box 8)
- Wisdom's Child New York Guide, The (Box 8)
  Subject: 1970s, Alternative local newspaper, Gay liberation movement
  Publisher: The Wisdoms Child NEW YORK GUIDE
- WIT: Women In Theatre Network (Box 8)
- WNY Q News (Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender & Transsexual) (Box 8)
  Subject: Alternative local newspaper, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender, Transsexual, 1990s
- Wolfe Video (Box 8)
  Publication City: New Almaden, CA
- Woman Lobbyist, The (Box 8)
  Subject: feminist
- Woman's Journal-Advocate (Box 8)
- Women and Family Law Newsletter (Box 8)
- Women in Martial Arts (Box 8)
- Women In Sunlight (Box 8)
- Women in the Martial Arts (Box 8)
  Publication City: Corpus Christi, TX
- Women in the Trades (Box 8)
- Women Networking Magazine (Box 8)
- Women Source (Box 8)
- Women Turnover: A Magazine of Food Issues (Box 8)
- Women/ Poems (Box 8)
  Publication City: Lexington, MA
- Women's Forum (Box 8)
  Subject: Heterosexual
  Publication City: New York,NY
- Womyn's Community News (Box 8)
- Womyns Weekly (Box 8)
- Womyn's Words (Box 8)
  Publisher: Women's Energy Bank, Inc.
  Publication City: St. Petersburg, FL
- Word, The (Box 8)
  Publication City: Indianapolis, IL
- Words of Women (Box 8)
- Workers World (Box 8)
- Workforce (Box 8)
- World of S&M (Box 8)
- Xanadu (Box 8)
  Publication City: Wantagh, NY
- Yellow Brick Road: Nesletter for Gay Services of Kansas (Box 8)
  Publication City: Lawrence, KS
- Your Gay News (Box 8)
- Youth Alternatives (National Youth Alternatives Project) (Box 8)
- Youth Magazine (Box 8)
- Zelda's Monthly (Box 8)
  Subject: Queer